I want to quit Love For Real.
我想退出《現戀》了
What?!
-什麼？
Right now?!
都錄一半了耶
Why are you saying this?!
怎麼突然說要退出呢？
Lately, the guys at school tease me.
最近啊，學校裡的男生老是嘲弄我
Like, "So you like those types of guys?"
說什麼“原來妳喜歡這種類型”
Nothing's scarier than openly showing your feelings for someone you like.
將自己對別人的喜歡袒露給所有人看 沒什麼比這個更可怕了
I had no idea until the show started.
在節目播出之前，我都體會不到
Drawing attention from many people isn't all good.
原來受人矚目並非全是好事
I do dumb stuff on my channel too, so I understand.
我也常在自己的頻道上裝傻耍寶 所以我能理解妳的心情
Everyone thinks I'm dumb… Well, in fact, I am dumb though.
大家都把我看成一個笨蛋 不過，我的確是挺笨的啦
A-Are you really going to quit?
妳真的要退出嗎？
I'll listen anytime you need to talk!
妳有心事的話可以隨時跟我說啊
If you're gonna quit, I'll quit too!
夕雪退出的話，我也不幹了
Nobu…
信行
So don't be like that. Let's continue!
別再說那種話了，留下來吧
I…
我…
WILL YUKI REALLY LEAVE THE SHOW?
（夕雪會從節目下車嗎？）
Wow, I wonder what's gonna happen!
接下來會怎麼樣呢？
She might really quit. Since Yuki seems sensitive.
可能真的會退出喔 感覺夕雪挺脆弱的
But what will happen to Nobu if she quits?!
但是，如果她真的退出的話 那信行怎麼辦？
YUKI SUMI TO QUIT DATING SHOW?
（鷲見夕雪考慮退出節目？）
Look! I'm in a news article!
你們看，有我的報導呢
You think I contributed a little in gaining viewers?
我應該有為提高收視率 做出貢獻了吧？
Probably.
應該吧
So, are you going to quit the show?
所以妳真的要退出嗎？
Well, I can't quit, can I? There's a contract.
嗯？不能退出吧？我們可是簽約了啊
What? So that was an act?
什麼？所以那只是在演戲嗎？
No, no, I'm not an actress like you, Kurokawa, so I can't act.
不是啦，我又不像黑川同學妳 我不是演員，不會演戲啦
I just exaggerated my feelings a little.
我只是稍微放大了我自己的心情而已
It's true that I was sad from being teased at school.
在學校被嘲笑而傷心，這是真的
And it's also true that I've thought about quitting.
想過要退出節目也是真的
Because this show is always filmed first thing in the morning.
因為每次都得一大早來錄節目啊
I'm always so sleepy.
我眼睛都睜不開啦
I see, so it's not a lie, but an exaggeration.
原來如此，那不是撒謊，只是誇張
An exaggeration, huh?
誇張啊？
Once we started opening up after some time passed on the show,
一起拍攝節目一段日子之後 大家都稍微熟絡了一些
everyone's character became clear.
也漸漸看透每個人的性格
The ones who are good at this.
得心應手的傢伙
The one who isn't two-faced but unique.
沒有心機，但個性鮮明的傢伙
The ones who aren't good on camera and has little appearance.
還有不擅長做節目 鏡頭都被剪掉的傢伙
Aqua! Let's go eat once we're done!
阿奎，拍完了一起吃個飯吧
No, I'm good. I have food at home.
我不去了，家裡有準備晚飯
Come on, let's go!
一起去嘛
Mem-cho says she'll treat us to yakiniku.
MEM說她要請我們吃烤肉喔
What?! I never said that!
什麼？我沒說過啊
I know that you gained new subscribers recently and you're loaded.
我都知道喔，妳的頻道訂閱人數 最近漲了不少，收入不錯呢
Your agency only takes 50% of the cut, right?
而且妳的事務所是五五分帳的吧？
Seriously?!
真的嗎？
We split 80/20 at my agency. I envy you.
我這邊是八二分帳，好羡慕喔
Ermm…
真是的…
All right! Add on another extra premium assortment!
好！再來一份特高級拼盤！
Stuff yourselves, brats!
給我盡情地吃，小鬼們！
Yay!
-好耶！
Aqua, the kainomi is cooked.
阿奎亞同學，牛腰脊心烤好了
I'll grill my own, so don't worry about me.
我自己來就行了，妳不用照顧我
Kurokawa, you haven't been eating at all.
而且妳從剛才開始就沒在吃啊
No, this is my role!
不，這正是我該做的事
I've decided to never release the tongs in these settings.
我已經決定好 在這種場合絕對不會放下烤肉夾的
People would get mad when I used to burn the meat before,
以前我常因為把肉烤焦而被駡
but I can grill them well now.
但我現在相當熟練了呢
That's why!
所以說啊
What's being demanded right now is something more extreme!
如今觀眾追求的 是更刺激的情節和內容
It's like, how much risk you take…
要看你願意承擔多少風險…
She's so studious.
好認真啊
Ah, I'm sure the yakiniku was luxurious.
這樣啊，去烤肉那麼奢侈啊
I bet the meat you ate while staring at some cute girls tasted real good, huh?
看著可愛女生吃的烤肉 一定特別美味吧？
Well, it was just a hangout.
還好吧，只是普通聚餐而已
Liar! I can see the satisfaction oozing out from your face!
騙人！ 你臉上都洋溢著滿足的神情呢！
No, it's not.
才沒有
Look me in my eyes and say that!
看著我的眼睛再說一次啊！
With a young body, you can eat unlimited oily foods and never get indigestion.
這副年輕的身軀無論吃下 多少油膩的食物都不會消化不良
This is too awesome.
簡直太爽了
You promised to eat with us on Sundays together.
明明約好了週日是一起吃晚飯的日子
But it's been like this ever since that show started!
但你自從出演節目之後就一直這樣
First of all, isn't that show's concept to meet after school?
話說回來，那節目的設定 不是下課後約會的高中生們嗎？
But they always film on weekends. It's a setup!
但你們都在週末進行拍攝 根本就是造假嘛！
It's not a big deal.
也沒那麼嚴重吧
They're good at least for prioritizing education.
以學業為優先是好事
Actually, reality dating shows aren't set up as much as you think.
而且，戀愛實境秀沒想像中那麼虛假
A few of them are obviously faking it,
雖然有幾個人很明顯是在演戲
but most of them are just trying to make themselves look good.
但大部分人也只是想 在鏡頭前呈現自己好的一面
Everyone does that in real life, don't they?
在現實生活中每個人都是這樣的啊
If you go on a group date, you can see the same thing.
一般聯誼活動上的參與者 也差不多都是這樣
I've never been to one, so I wouldn't know…
我又沒參加過聯誼，哪知道啊？
Then does everyone seriously fall in love?
那你們真的會愛上對方嗎？
That depends on the individual.
每個人的想法不一樣吧
You end up liking them surprisingly.
出乎意料地會喜歡上呢
But my fans are watching, so I want to keep it to a certain level on the show.
但我的粉絲們在看 所以在節目中得拿捏分寸才行
I do! It's kinda similar to getting close to a host at a host club!
會啊，就像對牛郎 認真起來的那種感覺吧
I shift into work mode when I'm on camera, so it's a little hard.
我一面對鏡頭就會進入工作模式 所以不太會吧
Out of the question. It's work.
不可能，這只是一份工作
I seriously can. I mean, wouldn't it be fun if it led up to marriage?
我肯定會喔 乾脆走到結婚那一步不也挺有趣嗎？
I don't know…
我不知道
I'm just barely fulfilling my role, so I don't have the room for that.
光是扮演好角色就費了我不少精力 哪有工夫考慮這些？
I never watched reality dating shows before, so I lacked knowledge on it.
我至今都沒看過戀愛實境秀 有點缺乏了解
I had a biased view, but its realism is enough for it to be the selling point.
所以一直都帶著偏見 不過，實境本身就是節目的賣點
Contrary to what I imagined, not a lot is set up.
造假的成分沒我想像中那麼多
And it's filmed to show the individuals' character just as they are.
反而比我想像的 更能直接展現各自的人格魅力
What's the matter? Isn't it a good thing that there aren't many setups?
你怎麼陷入沉思了？ 沒什麼造假的部分不是很好嗎？
It's good from the audience's view.
從觀眾的角度來看是好的
But lies are also the best way to protect yourself.
但是謊言是保護自己最大的武器
Well, it's probably a needless worry though.
不過嘛，是我想多了吧
Later on,
在此之後
the Yuki Sumi and Nobuyuki Kumano pair becomes the focus of the show.
鷲見夕雪和熊野信行 開始成為節目的拍攝重點
That's where Kengo shows his jealousy.
加上在一旁吃醋的劍吾
A love triangle is formed over Yuki.
形成了以夕雪為中心的三角關係
Yuki becomes the gamemaster,
夕雪成為這場戀愛遊戲的關鍵人物
and her flirty character excites the show.
跟男生們打情駡俏炒熱氣氛
And the show gradually gains popularity from teenagers.
漸漸提升節目 在國高中生群體中的人氣
Aqua, what about you?
阿奎，你呢？
Are you not gonna join the battle over Yuki?
你不加入夕雪的爭奪戰嗎？
If you wanna get popular, it's better to mingle with them instead of me.
想要走紅的話就別找我 多跟他們來往才是更正確的做法喔
I'm good. I want to play it safe until the show ends.
不用了 我想就這樣打安全牌，直到節目結束
You have no ambition…
還真沒有野心呢
What about you? Aren't you going to butt in?
那妳呢？不打算插一腳嗎？
As long as I can keep this dumb, laid-back role, I'm okay.
我只要能維持現在這種 呆萌療癒系的形象就很滿足了
Since my goal is to lead viewers to my own channel.
畢竟我的目標 是吸引觀眾訂閱我的頻道嘛
But if you wanna make a move on me seriously, now that's a different story.
不過，如果阿奎想要認真追求我的話 那就另當別論了
Don't get your hopes up.
期待不要太高喔
But the one we should be more worried about is…
但比起我們倆，更令人擔心的是…
She sells seashells by the seashore.
石獅寺前有四十四個石獅子
The shells she sells are sea-shells, I'm sure. For if she sells sea-shells…
寺前樹上結了四十四個澀柿子 四十四個石獅子…
-Excuse me… -Do you want to be fired?!
-經紀人… -你是不是不想幹啦？
I heard the reality show Akane's in was popular, so I watched it,
聽說小茜出演的實境秀人氣飆升 我就找來看了
but what the hell is that?!
那是怎麼回事啊？
She probably wasn't even on screen for ten minutes!
出場時間連十分鐘都不到！
This is her chance, but she isn't standing out one bit!
明明是個大好機會 但她居然毫不起眼
You're the manager! Why aren't you lecturing her?!
身為經紀人，你都沒好好督促她嗎？
But Boss, Akane is doing her best and--
但是，社長，小茜已經很努力…
Doing her best doesn't make any money!
光靠努力是掙不了錢的！
I chose her out of a ton of kids who said they wanted to do it!
想出演這個節目的孩子那麼多 我還是選了她
At least make her leave a mark on the show!
叫她至少在節目中給觀眾留下印象！
I'm sorry, Manager…
對不起，經紀人
Oh. You were listening?
哦，妳都聽到了？
Akane, you're doing the best you can, so don't worry.
小茜，妳已經盡力了，不要放在心上
I'll act as your shield for you.
我會好好替妳擋風遮雨的
I-It's because I'm not good enough…
都是因為我不爭氣…
I must work harder.
我得更努力才行
I need to work harder to leave a mark.
要更努力才能給觀眾留下印象
Ugh, this juice is gross.
好噁喔，這果汁超難喝
I'll post this on Twitter to get my money's worth.
得把這件事發佈到推特 這樣買果汁的錢才有價值
"The new drink I bought at the convenience store was ultra gross…"
“在便利商店買的 新上架果汁超難喝…”
Hey!
住手！
What was that for?
妳幹嘛打人啊？
What were you just trying to do?!
妳這是想幹什麼呢？
What if you write a bad comment about a company's product,
像這樣在網路上給人家的商品留負評
and they happened to be egosurfing?!
萬一那家公司自我搜尋怎麼辦？
No, they wouldn't.
不會啦
Jeez, you ex-commoners know nothing.
就說妳這些普通人一無所知吧
If you write about a product, at least five affiliated people will see it!
要是暴露了商品名稱 至少會被五個相關人士搜尋到
And that company will never offer you a job!
然後，就永遠不再有機會 接到那家公司的任何工作
You're exaggerating.
也太誇張了吧
Don't you egosurf yourself?
難道妳不會自我搜尋嗎？
No, I don't.
不會喔
Gimme your phone!
手機拿來！
Oh! Give it back!
等等！還給我！
Let's see.
讓我看看
That's a lot of digging.
搜了不少嘛
Oh my, you've even put "cute" in your search words.
什麼嘛 自己的關鍵詞還搜了“好可愛”啊
Did you wanna see people call you cute that much?
就那麼想聽人說自己可愛嗎？
Everyone says they don't egosurf, but let me state this!
雖然大家嘴上都說沒有 但我敢肯定地說
Ninety percent of idols all egosurf!
有九成的偶像都會自我搜尋！
Try going to a wrap party after an event.
只要去過一次 工作結束後的慶功酒會就知道了
It's funny how all musicians and performers are egosurfing as they drink.
無論是樂團成員還是演員 都在邊喝酒邊自我搜尋，挺有趣的喔
Whoa.
這樣啊
The world has entered a great egosurf era!
如今已是大自搜時代！
You can now access big data without being an advertising agency,
就算不是廣告公司 也能輕易使用大數據
so you can look up analytics on reviews and target audience!
每個人都可以自行查看 評論和客群的分析數據
Web advertising now costs as much as traditional ads
數位廣告的開銷已經追上傳統廣告
and is said to be a two-trillion-yen market!
據說市場規模已達兩兆日圓
The days of ignoring internet responses have ended.
無視網友反應的時代已經過去了
The ones who lack online marketing are the ones to retire first in society now.
在現在的社會時局裡 不善於網路行銷的人將最先被淘汰
The content creators and the fans are now mutually monitoring each other.
內容創作者和粉絲之間 處於一個相互監視的狀態
And in this industry, we are the content itself.
而在演藝圈內，我們本身就是內容
Don't forget that if you gaze long into an abyss, the abyss also gazes into you.
千萬記住 在妳凝視深淵之時，深淵也在凝視妳
AKANE'S NONEXISTENT
（說不上喜歡或討厭）
YUKI'S CUTE AKANE'S NONEXISTENT…
（夕雪好可愛啊 小茜的存在感也太低了）
I gotta work harder.
我得更努力才行
What are you doing?
你們在幹嘛？
I was taking a video for the show's official Twitter and TikTok accounts.
我們在拍攝短片 上傳到節目的官方推特和抖音帳號
Hm.
這樣啊
We've been gaining lots of subscribers. Well, that's all thanks to me of course!
追蹤人數漲了不少呢 當然，這全是多虧有我啦
Speaking of which, Mem, weren't you originally a TikToker?
對了，MEM一開始 是在抖音起家的嘛
Yup. There was no affiliate marketing or Coins at the time,
是啊，不過，當時沒有廣告收入 也沒有打賞
so I switched over to being a YouTuber.
我就轉向YouTube啦
Aqua, you upload something too!
阿奎，你也來上傳點什麼吧
I don't know how to use those platforms for the youngsters, so it's okay.
我不太會用這種年輕人的玩意 還是算了吧
You old-timer!
像個大叔似的
Huh?
嗯？
Nobu, do you wanna go over there together?
信行，可以一起過去嗎？
Akane's making a move!
小茜採取行動了呢
I forgot about this girl.
我都忘了還有一個女生
Was it Akane?
好像叫小茜吧
Whether she's there or not, isn't it the same?
小茜在不在好像都沒差吧
They can kick out Akane, so please add a new guy member!
把小茜踢走，多加一個男生嘛
"What should I do to stand out?"
該怎麼做才能嶄露頭角？
Well, that's where you pull a bad girl move and steal Nobu from Yuki.
這個嘛，當然是扮演壞女孩的角色 從夕雪手上把信行搶過來啊
If you can do that, your character will stand out and you'll draw attention.
要是能做到這點 肯定能建立鮮明的形象，吸引關注
Of course, that's not a direction or anything.
當然，這也不是指示什麼的
But the kids that can do that are the ones who become popular.
不過，能做到這點的孩子肯定能紅
I gotta work harder…
我得更努力才行
Wow! How pretty!
哇，好漂亮啊！
My big sister's a manicurist, so I learned this from her.
我姐姐是美甲師 這是我從她那裡學的
That's cool.
好厲害喔
Akane, I'll do yours too.
小茜，我也幫妳做吧
Come here.
過來
Uh, okay.
嗯，好啊
Akane, are you panicking lately?
小茜，妳最近是不是很急躁啊？
The series is almost finished, so I can understand.
畢竟節目就快到尾聲了 我也能理解妳的心情
It's not exactly like that.
也不是因為這個
I just want to stand out to produce results, that's all.
我只是想顯眼一些 做點成績出來，僅此而已
I see.
這樣啊
But I can't let you.
但我是不會輕易讓路的
I'm going to fight for the spotlight myself.
我會為了那道耀眼的光環而戰鬥
So don't think badly of me.
妳可別怪我喔
YUKI LIKE #LOVE_FOR_REAL "I BET YUKI HAS A GOOD PERSONALITY"
（搜尋：夕雪《現戀》 感覺夕雪本人的性格也那麼好）
AKANE LIKE #LOVE_FOR_REAL NO SEARCH RESULTS
（搜尋：小茜《現戀》 無搜尋結果）
I wonder why I'm so different from Yuki.
為什麼我跟夕雪 之間的差別那麼大呢？
I need to stand out more than her.
我必須比夕雪更顯眼才行
And so then--
然後啊…
Ken!
劍！
You said you liked Labradors, right? There's a big one over there!
你說過你喜歡拉布拉多犬，對吧？ 那邊有一隻很大的拉布拉多喔
Oh, seriously?!
真的假的？
I need to work hard and fight.
我必須拼命戰鬥才行
For the sake of everyone supporting me too.
就算是為了對我抱有期待的人而努力
-Let's go! -Stop it!
-走吧 -妳夠了！
Clinging to guys so easily!
總是隨隨便便往男人身上貼
You play too dirty…
妳的手段未免太…
Cut!
卡！
We'll stop the shoot once!
先暫停錄影！
Get a towel or tissues!
去拿毛巾或紙巾之類的
Doing that to a model's face is a bit much…
那樣弄傷模特兒的臉有點太過分了吧
She has a magazine shoot tomorrow, right?
明天不是還有雜誌拍攝嗎？
I… I… didn't mean to… No…
我不是故意的，怎麼會…
Akane.
小茜
I…
我…
Akane!
小茜！
I'm okay, so calm down!
我沒事，妳冷靜一點
I understand, you just panicked. I know that you're a hard worker, Akane.
我明白，妳只是有點急躁，對吧？ 小茜的努力我都知道喔
You were trying to meet everyone's expectations
妳為了滿足大家的期待
and did something out of your comfort zone so you got all confused, right?
才會去嘗試自己不擅長的事 結果搞得自己也不知所措了，對吧？
Sorry… Your face… And you have a magazine shoot…
對不起，妳的臉… 明明還有雜誌拍攝…
Don't worry.
沒關係
This will be easily erased in Photoshop, so it won't affect work!
這種小傷稍微修圖一下就能掩蓋住 不會影響我的工作的
Akane, do you hate me?
小茜，妳討厭我嗎？
I don't hate you.
不討厭
You're strong and kind, I like you.
妳又堅強又溫柔，我很喜歡呢
Me too. I like you and your hardworking, earnest self.
我也是喔，我也很喜歡 努力不懈、凡事竭盡全力的小茜
That's why I won't get mad.
所以我才不會生氣呢
Really?
真的嗎？
The camera isn't rolling, so there's no point in acting right now.
攝影機又沒在拍 這種時候我沒必要演戲啊
If this were school,
如果是在學校
arguing a little and making up would be a common story.
像這樣有點小爭吵 又馬上和好的事情經常發生
But even if the conflict is resolved amongst themselves…
可是即使當事人已經私下解決…
AKANE WHO LAID A HAND ON YUKI…
（對夕雪動手的小茜…）
AKANE KUROKAWA
（黑川茜）
AKANE MUST BE WORSE OFF CAMERA…
（黑川茜本人一定更惡劣）
SHE NEEDS TO BE ARRESTED…
（必須報警逮捕）
THE DULL GIRL EMERGES…
（樸素女行動了）
I KNEW SHE WAS CRAZY…
（我就知道她不對勁）
AKANE'S DONE THIS BEFORE…
（以前也做過這種事吧）
SHE'S SO TRASHY LOL
（簡直爛透了）
…the internet won't allow it.
網友也絕不原諒
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING!
（感謝大家收看）
POST YOUR REVIEW BY TWEETING #LOVE_FOR_REAL
（記得標註“現戀” 在推特上發佈評論喔）
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
（真是個扯後腿的）
DON'T EVER SHOW YOUR FACE AGAIN.
（別再讓我看到妳的臉）
WHY DID THE SHOW USE HER?
（節目組為什麼會用她啊？）
WHO'S AKANE AGAIN? LOL
（黑川茜是誰啊？）
THE WORST ON THE SHOW.
（節目中最糟糕的傢伙）
PLEASE QUIT ALREADY.
（快消失吧）
"I knew it," is what I thought.
“果然變成這樣了”，我是這麼想的
I thought I'd be forgiven if I apologized properly.
本以為只要好好道歉，就能得到原諒
I AM TRULY SORRY…
（真的十分抱歉…）
Due to my contract with the show,
礙於跟節目組簽的合約
I can't say anything about things that weren't filmed,
我不能說出任何沒有播出的內容
but if I just explain as much as I can and apologize…
但我想只要把能說的都說出來 盡可能解釋，然後道歉的話…
But that triggered it.
沒想到卻成了導火線
-You make me want to puke. -Be sorry you were born.
-看到妳的臉就想吐 -為自己的出生道歉吧
-Aren't you ashamed to be alive? -You think an apology is enough?
-妳這樣活著不羞恥嗎？ -以為道歉就夠了嗎？
Mem told me before…
MEM這麼說過…
People gang up on those who apologize.
人們總是會圍攻那些道歉的人
"If you apologize, you admit that you did something bad, right?"
“既然道歉 就表示你確實做壞事了吧？”
"We can punish you if you did something bad."
“既然做了壞事 那朝你扔石頭也是合理的吧？”
That's what they think.
他們就是這種想法
While apologizing is the ethically correct choice as a Japanese person,
雖然在日本人的價值觀裡 謝罪這種行為是正確的
it's the absolute worst thing you could do in response to backlash.
但面對排山倒海的惡評 道歉是最糟糕的回應
REPENT BY DYING
（以死謝罪吧）
I did something bad, so I deserve it.
我的確做了壞事，這也是罪有應得
This is everyone's opinion… I shouldn't look away from it.
這些是大家的意見，我不應該無視的
I even looked through the criticisms as much as possible.
我連對我的惡評也都盡可能看了一遍
Backlash is something that hits the serious people harder.
對於炎上這種事 越是認真的人受的傷害就越深
They shouldn't even look at the criticisms.
明明不要去看惡評就好了
But they try to earnestly accept everyone's opinion head-on.
認真的人 卻總是想真摯地接受所有意見
When I close my eyes, I can't think of anything but the backlash.
就算閉上眼睛 腦子裡也只想到那些批評指責的留言
So I tell myself that it'll calm down by morning and force myself to sleep.
我只能安慰自己，等明天一早醒來 一切都會恢復平靜，強迫自己入睡
But there's no way that would happen.
但是，那是不可能發生的事
Akane, are you okay?
小茜，妳還好嗎？
You look pale.
氣色看起來不太好喔
I'm fine.
我沒事
You want to stay home tomorrow?
明天跟學校請假吧？
I'm fine, I'll go to school.
不用了，我會去的
You see Akane's news?
妳有看到小茜那件事嗎？
Isn't it crazy? I knew she'd do something like this one day.
很糟糕吧？ 我就知道她總有一天會做出這種事
She always acts like a celebrity, saying she has work and stuff.
老是說自己有工作 擺出一副明星的模樣
Does she always have to act like she's better than us?
她那樣是想要 突顯出自己比我們優秀嗎？
Such an ugly personality.
性格真的糟透了
She always gives off this vibe like, "I'm different from all of you."
她總是散發出一種 “我跟你們這種人不一樣”的氛圍
I bet her posse of guys are soothing her now.
現在肯定在讓 那群討好她的男生安慰她吧
I bet.
一定是吧
Akane, you seem down lately. Is something wrong?
小茜，妳最近看起來沒什麼精神 怎麼了嗎？
Did something happen at work?
工作上遇到什麼事了嗎？
No.
沒有啊
These trashy hoes are born because their moms don't teach them anything.
就是因為當媽媽的都沒好好教育 才會養出這種賤女人嘛
It's a cycle!
簡直是負面的連鎖反應
I'm sorry, Mom…
對不起，媽媽
For now, it's probably best to not tweet anything right now.
總而言之，眼下先不要發推特比較好
Anything you say will just fuel the fire. If you want to post something, tell me.
不管妳說什麼，都只是火上添油 如果想發言的話，先找我商量
When a new episode released, I didn't have the energy to check the comments.
新一集節目播出當天 我連確認內容的精力都沒有
But after seeing the backlash reignite like before,
但看到稍微平靜的惡評聲浪 又再次沸騰起來
I was able to guess what they'd said.
我就大概能猜到節目的內容了
And I also figured this will never settle as long as this show is popular,
而且，我也意識到只要這個節目 還在受人矚目，這件事就不會平息
and that it's a problem that will haunt me for the rest of my showbiz career.
並且會在 我接下來的演藝生涯中如影隨形
I know her from a long time ago,
我很久以前就認識她了
but she thinks she's different from everyone else around her.
她總覺得自己跟周邊的人不一樣
She probably believes she's a genius or something.
大概是認為自己是天才之類的
I doubt she would ever think about the pain of others.
我想她應該沒考慮過其他人的痛楚呢
Those goody-goody moves are all just an act too, right?
平時的乖寶寶模樣 也全是演出來的吧？
I'm sure she's just partying with guys in secret
她背地裡都在跟男人鬼混
and never working that seriously.
並沒有在認真工作吧
She always has a face on like she's the center of the world.
老是擺出一副 “我就是世界中心”的樣子
I bet she's just a rich kid anyway, she's never suffered any hardships.
肯定只是個 沒經歷過什麼大風大浪的富二代吧
Is there anyone who likes this brat?
有人會喜歡這樣的傢伙嗎？
These types of kids are useless no matter what they do.
這種人不管幹什麼都沒用
I bet she doesn't have friends.
她肯定沒有朋友吧
You can tell how shallow she is since she can't get along with others.
跟身邊的人都處不來 你就知道她有多膚淺了啊
She's an idiot who doesn't think about consequences.
只不過是個做事不考慮後果的蠢蛋嘛
She's always surrounded by guys
身邊總是被男生圍繞
and throws a fit if she doesn't get her way, right?
只要有什麼不合心意 就亂發大小姐脾氣
She's probably never dedicated herself to anything in her life.
她肯定也沒試過 為某件事全心全意地付出吧
I see these types of selfish brats around me too.
我身邊也有這種任性的傢伙啊
Narcissist. You don't belong anywhere.
自戀狂，這裡已經容不下妳了
This Akane who's been getting backlash is the main cast at Theater Lalalai
現在被炎上的那個黑川茜 是拉拉萊劇團的主要演員
and she's a super hard worker.
是個努力上進的孩子
But after seeing this incident, it makes me feel like everything was faked.
但看到這次的騷動之後 讓我覺得那應該只是人設吧
I've been supporting her all this time, but I can't anymore.
我一直以來都很支持她呢 現在再也沒辦法了
I was Akane's classmate up to middle school, but everyone seriously hated her.
我跟小茜是國中的同班同學 確實所有人都很討厭她呢
I hear she messes around and is a slut too.
聽說她都跟男人鬼混，私生活超亂的
She's completely finished as a celebrity.
身為一名藝人 這可說是徹底完蛋了呢
Nobody would use someone who'd hit a model's face.
不可能會有人願意 用一個弄傷模特兒臉蛋的人吧
Isn't she ugly too?
是說，她長得好醜啊
She does look like she has a rotten personality.
看起來就是一副性格惡劣的樣子
Bye-bye, Akane. Too bad we'll never see you on TV anymore.
再會啦，小茜 很遺憾，妳不會再有上電視的機會囉
NAMELESS ANONYMOUS: SIMPLY PUT, DIE
（無名氏：趕緊去死吧）
YOU OKAY? YOU EATING?
（信行：小茜沒事吧？吃飯沒？）
EVERYONE'S WORRIED ABOUT YOU
（MEM：大家都很擔心妳呢）
Oh yeah, I haven't eaten anything.
對了，我還沒吃呢
I'LL GO BUY SOME FOOD
（我現在去買點吃的）
DON'T GO LOL A TYPHOON'S COMING LOL
（信行：先別去啦w 現在在刮颱風呢w）
I'm tired.
好累
I'm tired… of thinking.
一直在思考，真的太累了
I don't want to think anymore.
我不要再想東想西的了
No! Let me go!
不！放開我！
Calm down!
冷靜一點！
I don't mean you any harm. Please just calm down.
我不是來傷害妳的 求妳了，先冷靜下來
Subtitle translation by: Kanami Kitabayashi
字幕翻譯：蔡曉琳